## JEFFERSON GRIEBEL

Gainesville, Florida

352.214.4762 | <u>Jefferson.griebel@gmail.com</u>
https://www.linkedin.com/in/jefferson-griebel/

### Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with five years of Software Testing with a lifelong passion for technology and learning. Effective at using creativity and problem solving in teams or on my own to complete complex tasks in the necessary time frame.

#### Technical Skills

**Technical Languages:** Git, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Cypress, React, graphql, RestAPIs, Redux, Node, MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Sequelize, jQuery.

Applications: Postman, GitHub, Heroku, JIRA, VSCode, MongoDB Compass, Figma, Docker

## **Projects**

# Code Collectives | https://github.com/jcg0/code-collective-project-3 | https://code-collectives.herokuapp.com/

- Code Collectives is a social media app that allows users to connect with each other and share user created posts to keep in touch with each other.
- For this application we had a group of three people, and my primary responsibilities
  were setting up our server and database on the backend and the profile page on the
  front end.
- In this project our team used React.js for the front end and linked that with that backend of node and graphal using Apollo server.

# Sweet Solution | https://github.com/EarlofSmith/sweet-solution | https://sweet-solution.herokuapp.com/

- Sweet Solution is an ecommerce app focused on providing baked goods to customers. Customers can view a store page and view items and item descriptions and add item quantities.
- My responsibility with this application was setting up the backend and creating the Login and Signup pages.
- For this project our group used Handlebars.js and HTML for the front-end MySQL for the backend.

## Experience

## **Quality Assurance Engineer - Remote**

2021-Present

TapGoods Dallas, Texas

Test and release state of the art online rental software. Create tests using an automated test environment with CircleCl and Cypress. Test and release bug fixes for clients weekly. Work in teams using AGILE and Kanban.

 Participate in drastically reducing client churn and reduce the frequency of bug discovery within the application.

Associate Engineer 1 2018-2021

Mobiquity Gainesville, Florida

Tested and released quality software for an FDA approved digital medicine application. Using automated and manual testing practices within the scope of the SDLC. Extensive Postman knowledge and use to test our applications APIs.

Produce Clerk 2012-2018

Publix Inc. Gainesville, Florida

Full-time employee where I used extensive customer service skills and working with a tightknit team to provide service for customers. Also handled inventory forecasting and employee scheduling for the department.

#### Education

### Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp Certificate: University of Denver

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js, and ReactJS.

**Associate degree in computer science:** Santa Fe College